Very good morning friends you are with
vanna kasana on quiz show name drive safer
mission possible yes we can a we can we are on
the mission to make our drives safer so
together we make it possible so here I am back with
very interesting question of the day
it's a second question you can come and
join this quiz show and answer your questions
and win more more exciting prizes
so here on my screen your second
question as you can see on my screen the
question is visible main aap log liye rahe hain
you are driving at 100 km pai
r on the road that has a limit of 80 km pai r there is
no camera and police you
will a continue to drive at 100 km pai
r b slow down to the speed limit c
increase your speed d proceed carefree carefully
and increase speed a main ek baar
hindi me padh diti hai aap log liye
aap a  You are going on the road at a speed of 100 km/hr
but the speed limit is
80 km/hr. There
is no camera and no policeman there, so what will you do? Will
you continue driving at a speed of 100 km/hr
or will you slow
down and reduce the speed limit or will
you increase your speed further or will
you carefully drive ahead and increase your speed. So
come as quickly as possible and participate in it,
give your answers and
you can win many exciting
prizes. Today is our third day of this quiz show.
Many winners have come, many
entries have come, many people have
participated in this show and won many
exciting and safety gifts. The
most interesting thing about this
quiz show is that every day we will
give you five questions every two hours,
which you can answer and
win exciting prizes. And
in every quiz, that means you will win five out of five.  You can
participate in the questions. There's no
restriction that you can participate in only one.
You can participate in all five questions and win
safety gear for yourself and your family.
Today is the third day of our quiz show, which will continue
until February 18th.
Come and participate.
Win exciting
prizes. To find out the results,
you can log in at night.
We have a show on our channel around 10 pm called
Bluntly Speaking. The results are announced in that show.
You can come and
see your winner's
name on my screen.
Come and register your answer.
You can enter a question only once.
You can't enter a question repeatedly.
But you can participate in the rest of our questions.
This is the
second question of the day. It's visible to you for two hours.
You can come and participate for two hours.
After two hours, our new anchor will come
and share a new question with you.
You can also answer the questions by visiting our website and Facebook
page.
As you all know that this
is our mission, as I told you, its name itself
is Drive Safer Mission Possible. How can we
make our mission possible by driving safely,
that is,
we go out on the roads on a daily basis,
so many people are on the roads with us,
everyone uses the roads, the roads are for everyone, so
how can we make those roads safe?
If you look at foreign countries,
our roads are very safe, that is, the
driving sense of the people on the foreign roads is amazing
and they
maintain a distance, in these cases, if someone suddenly
applies the brakes, they have enough time and
space to save their vehicle. And as
we  As you
can see this question, it is already given
that you are travelling at a speed of 100 kmph
and the speed
limit there is 80 kmph but you are travelling at a speed of 100 kmph
because there
is no camera and no policeman there.
We should always set one thing in our mind,
we should understand
that these speed limits, these
cameras, these safety gears,
safety measures which have been given to us are
for our safety and
not for anyone else. So, just to avoid the camera
or to show off to the police, you
wear seat belts or helmets
or you travel within the speed limit, you are
not doing it for them, all those
things are for you, so we request
you to take care of your things, the
safety helmets, safety gears that you are using are
not for anyone else, you should
always keep in mind that you are doing it only for your own
life and the life of your loved ones.
We talk about if like helmets
If you are going on a two wheeler, then
you should take a helmet because it has been seen in many places that
people do
not buy helmets after asking for ISI, they do
not buy good quality ones, they just wear them to
show off to the police men, which
is not right,
you should take all those measures not for the police men but to protect yourself from any mishappening,
or for example, if
we talk about speed limits, the
speed limits given on the roads are basically given after looking at the
crowd on that road, how much
traffic is there or how many pedestrians are using it
or whether there is any such area from
where any animal can come on the road, so we
request
you to follow those rules, you should
look at the sign boards when you are driving
because there are many sign
boards given on the road,
main network slopes, turns, so if
you take care of those things then
somewhere we can make our roads safe along with
ourselves.  We can save the lives of others as well
because we do not know
our speed limit, that is,
if we suddenly apply brakes at 100 kmph, then
how much damage can be caused, you all know this, so
we are requesting you that you should understand all the
things related to road safety, this is our
entire campaign related to road safety,
what is road safety, road safety is like a road,
road is itself safe, nothing happens to the roads,
roads are always safe, but for those who are
using them, those who are walking on them, those who
use them on a daily basis,
we have to make the roads safe for them
and who will make that, we will make it
because when we are using it, if we
follow all the rules on the roads,
if we use the roads properly, then
somewhere or the other we can bring changes,
like in cars or
otherwise, it happens very quickly, like if you
see that if we keep the cars by maintaining a distance,
you must have seen at the
red lights and all, so  Those who ride two
wheelers try to
go ahead every day by taking out even small spaces,
those people do not understand this
because you are on a bike, you are on a two wheeler,
your exposed area is
very large and it becomes very
risky, if anything goes wrong
or an accident happens then the
chances of you people getting damaged are
very high, so I think there is a great need for those people to be careful
and we request that those who
use two wheelers, please take some
care, if someone is sitting behind them
or even they themselves
because your life is most important,
so please take some care,
drive in your lane, wear proper helmets,
wear proper jackets in gloves so that you can
save yourself from anything going wrong,
it is very
important, let us talk about our quiz show,
you can see the question on my screen,
please come and register yourself
along with your
loved ones  Ask your family members,
friends and those you love to
participate in this. It's
not just for the gifts, it's for the two of you to increase your
knowledge about road safety so that you can make them
aware and tell them
how you can keep yourself and the people you love safe. Let me
read this question for you once again which is on my screen.
You are driving at 100 kmph on a
road that has a limit of 80 kmph.
You are driving at a speed of 100 kmph on a
road whose speed
limit is 80 kmph but there is
no camera and no police there.
What will you do? A. Continue to drive
at 100 kmph. You will
continue at the speed of 100 kmph. B. Slow down
to the speed limit. You will slow down your
speed from 100 kmph.  At 80 km/h,
increase your speed at R speed. You will
increase your speed because there
is no camera or policeman there. Proceed carefully and increase your
speed. You will be careful and
move ahead and increase your speed.
So join us and see,
join this campaign and participate,
give your answers and enhance your
knowledge related to road safety and
you have a chance to win many exciting gifts.
Win them and not only yourself, you mean
your loved ones, whom you love,
your friends, your family
members, you can also ask them to participate in this and
you have a chance to win many exciting gifts.
Come and win and let us join us and
make our roads safe together because these
roads, our roads, belong to
all of us. It is our responsibility to
make them safe and
follow our rules. If everyone
follows their own rules, then we will make our
roads safe.  We will make them safe, there are so many crashes, so many
road accidents, there is so much
loss,
we can save ourselves from that,
we do not say that
you are responsible for the accidents that happen on the roads every day,
but somewhere you are definitely a partner in that thing, so
change yourself, change your road behaviour and
join us in this campaign and
bring about a change,
so let me tell you once again by
reading this question,
you are driving at 100 km, you are on the
road that has a limit of 80 km, there is
no camera and the police, you will continue
to drive at 100 km, you
slow down to the speed limit, increase your speed, proceed carefully
and increase the speed, so you see,
come and participate
and for a day, thank you so much, we will meet
soon after two hours with a new set of
questions, stay safe, stay healthy, stay
tuned, so I thank you so much, otherwise please see you
on